<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>r-gis on Spatial Analysis with R</title>
    <link>https://gisma-courses.github.io/moc-rgis/categories/r-gis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in r-gis on Spatial Analysis with R</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gisma-courses.github.io/moc-rgis/categories/r-gis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://gisma-courses.github.io/moc-rgis/post/2021-10-12-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gisma-courses.github.io/moc-rgis/post/2021-10-12-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Spatial Analysis with R Motivation “Everything is related to everything else, but near things are more related than distant things” (Tobler, 1970). With this sentence, Waldo R. Tobler made geographic history, although his main concern was to reduce the complexity of his population simulation model so that it could be calculated at all on the IT infrastructure of the 1970s. Fifty years later, society is facing other major challenges. Environmental and climate change is leading to species loss rates comparable only to the great mass extinctions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space needs a Scope</title>
      <link>https://gisma-courses.github.io/moc-rgis/post/2021-10-12-space-needs-a-scope/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gisma-courses.github.io/moc-rgis/post/2021-10-12-space-needs-a-scope/</guid>
      <description>.myDiv {margin-top: -30px;margin-right: -40%; text-align: right;} Source: Dr. John Snow via wikimedia
 Approaching the topic of spatio-temporal relationships and how to represent them digitally seems problematic for both beginners and experts. In general, it involves perceiving spatial patterns and interactions in order to arrive at an understanding and description of the underlying processes. This is a scientifically based, abstract, cognitive, spatially focused experience of the world that provides the basis for understanding environmental change, assessing consequences and deriving responses or solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
